(Alicia:)They're happy, I get stuff.
Who cares? And how is it
any different from what you do?
(Penny:)Excuse me?
(Alicia:)I've seen you around them.
(Alicia:)Are you pretending
like you don't do the exact same thing?
(Penny:)Okay, lady, you are way out of line.
- Oh, I'm out of line?
- Yeah, you're out of line.
Well, what are you gonna do about it,
bitch?
(Raj:)I like Green Lantern.
(Raj:)I'm just saying it's pretty lame
that he can be defeated by the color yellow.
(Sheldon:)Only the modern Green Lantern
is vulnerable to yellow.
Golden-age Green Lantern
was vulnerable to wood.
(Raj:)Great, so I can take them both out
with a number-two pencil?
[PENNY AND ALICIA SCREAMING]
Oh, my God. Girl fight!
(Leonard:)What are you doing?
(Howard:)I know you.
You're stupid enough to break it up.